postbulletin.com 2018-10-13

# Privacy Policy | Site | postbulletin.com

POSTBULLETIN.COM PRIVACY POLICY EFFECTIVE MARCH 26, 2018

INFORMATION GATHERED BY POSTBULLETIN.COM

This is the POSTBULLETIN.COM's ("PostBulletin") online privacy policy. This policy applies only to activities PostBulletin engages in on its website and does not apply to PostBulletin activities that are "offline" or unrelated to the website. PostBulletin collects certain anonymous data regarding the usage of the website. This information does not personally identify users, by itself or in combination with other information, and is gathered to improve the performance of the website. The anonymous data collected by the PostBulletin website can include information such as the type of browser you are using, your IP address and the length of the visit to the website.

You may also be asked to provide personally identifiable information on the PostBulletin website, which may include your name, address, telephone number, credit card number, and e-mail address. This information can be gathered when feedback or e-mails are sent to PostBulletin or when you register for services. In all such cases you have the option of providing us with personally identifiable information.

POSTBULLETIN.COM AND THIRD-PARTY COOKIES

Cookies are small bits of data that are deposited on a user's hard drive. The PostBulletin website utilizes Cookies and IP addresses for certain functions. Cookies permit users to store their password and other user information without having to constantly re-enter this data. Cookies also permits PostBulletin and our third-party advertisers to tailor our website and advertising to your needs. Most browsers permit users to decline to accept Cookies, although the default setting is typically to accept them. You may choose to decline the Cookies, but certain functions of the website may not be accessible to you.

CHOICES REGARDING TARGETED ADVERTISING

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Website. These companies may use information (not including any Personally-Identifying Information) about your visits to the website and other websites that are contained in Web Cookies in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For example, these technologies help us determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before, tailor ads to you if you have visited our site before, and in some cases avoid sending you duplicate advertisements. You can learn more about certain types of targeted advertising by visiting the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) website or [Ad Choices](http://youradchoices.com/).

In addition to disabling cookies and other tracking technologies, you may opt-out of receiving targeted advertising from participating ad networks, audience segment providers, ad serving vendors, and other service providers by visiting websites operated by the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) and [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/) .

ANALYTICS AND PERSONALIZATION

The services contained in this section enable PostBulletin to monitor and analyze web traffic and can be used to keep track of User behavior.

Google Analytics (Google)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

Google may use the Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

Opt out (https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION

PostBulletin typically does not directly sell personally identifiable information, such as your name or e-mail address to advertisers. However, non-personal "aggregated data" is used to enhance the operation of our website, analyze interest in the areas of our website and to inform our advertisers about the number of users that have viewed their advertising. Moreover, we may in some circumstances disclose personally identifiable information to third parties to enhance your experience on our website. Additionally, if you provide PostBulletin with content for publishing or feedback, we may publish your user name or other identifying data. PostBulletin may also disclose personally identifiable information in order to respond to a subpoena, court order or other such request. PostBulletin may also provide such personally identifiable information in response to a law enforcement agency's request or as otherwise required by law, including in response to a subpoena or court order. Your personally identifiable information may be provided to a third party if PostBulletin files for bankruptcy, or there is a transfer of the assets or ownership of PostBulletin in connection with proposed or consummated corporate reorganizations, such as mergers or acquisitions.

OTHER WEBSITES

PostBulletin is not responsible for the privacy policies of websites to which it links. If you provide any information to such third parties different rules regarding the collection and use of your personal information may apply. We strongly suggest you review such third party's privacy policies before providing any data to them.

SECURITY

PostBulletin takes appropriate steps to ensure data privacy and security including through various hardware and software methodologies. However, PostBulletin cannot guarantee the security of any information that is disclosed online.

CHILDREN

PostBulletin does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. PostBulletin requests that children under the age of 13 not submit any personal information to the website. Do not send any information about yourself to us - including information like your name, address or email address. Since information regarding children under the age of 13 is not collected, PostBulletin does not knowingly distribute personal information regarding children under the age of 13. In general, we do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If, in limited circumstances, we do knowingly collect personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we make a special effort to encourage children under the age of 13 to consult with their parents before furnishing any personal data.

OTHER

If you registered to receive email from PostBulletin, we may send you emails about PostBulletin products, promotions, or services as well as on behalf of other companies. You may change your preferences for the future at any time by using the unsubscribe instructions located near the bottom of any of our email newsletters. You will receive special offers via email from PostBulletin consistent with your stated personal preferences. PostBulletin also does research on our visitors' demographics, interests and behavior based on the information you provide to us including upon registration, from our server log files or from surveys. We do this to better understand and serve our visitors. This research is compiled and analyzed on an aggregated basis and PostBulletin may share this aggregated data with advertisers or other businesses. If you told us that you would be interested in receiving email from us, we may send you emails about PostBulletin products, promotions, or services as well as on behalf of other companies. In addition, in each advertising email you will be provided an ability to opt-out of receiving future emails from the specific advertiser.

CORRECTIONS AND UPDATES

If you wish to modify or update any information PostBulletin has received, please contact webmaster@POSTBULLETIN.COM. Please note that the PostBulletin website also contains public information that is gathered from a variety of official public notices and governmental agencies. PostBulletin simply reproduces this information and users who feel that any public information contained on the PostBulletin website is inaccurate should contact the appropriate governmental agency or other source to correct this information.

MODIFICATIONS OF THE PRIVACY POLICY

PostBulletin reserves the rights to modify its privacy policy at any time and will notify you by posting an amendment to the privacy policy on the website. Such modifications will become effective on the day they are posted. PostBulletin encourages you to frequently review the privacy policy for any modifications.
